This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption
and shameful acts are not encouraged.
Please view this as a comedy.
Furthermore, all characters appearing
in this work are of legal age.
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner
is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing
as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence
or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised.
Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products
is intended. The Content Provider, the producers
and related parties shall have no liability,
as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability
for any purpose of the information provided in this work.
The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect
the views and opinions of the Content Provider,
or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
This is Iori-chan! She's new here!
（男）新人の伊織(いおり)ちゃんでーす
She just started college this spring!
この春 大学生になったばかりの
ピチピチですよ～
Welcome! Thanks for requesting me today!
（伊織）いらっしゃいませ
（伊織）本日は
ご指名ありが… えっ!?
（２人）ヒヒ…
（伊織）ギャー！
ハァ ハァ… 夢か…
It was just a dream...
What a nightmare!
まったく ひどい夢だ
I would never wear a high school girl's uniform.
俺が女子高生の制服なんか
着るわけ…
Good morning.
おはようございます… ぬっ！
（２人）おはよう
ヒッ… イヤー！
No!
Be passionate, my friends
♪～
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
Grand Blue Dreaming
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
～♪
ああ…
I didn't know you guys were into that sort of thing...
まさか 先輩たちに
そんな趣味があっただなんて
What are you talking about, Iori?
（寿(ことぶき)）はあ？
何言ってるんだ 伊織
That uniform...
（伊織）だって その制服！
I like uniforms, but why did you give me
a boy's uniform?
（耕平(こうへい)）制服は好きですが
なんで男子高校生用なんですか！
I thought we'd focus on our club activities today.
（時田(ときた)）今日は真面目に
サークル活動をしようと思ってな
（伊織･耕平）え？
Good morning. Huh?
（千紗(ちさ)）おはよう… えっ？
Uniforms...
（耕平）うーむ 確かに…
Perverts.
（千紗）変態
（伊織）違うぞ 千紗！
-It's not what you think, Chisa!
-They told us they're for diving!
これをダイビングに使うと
渡されて！
Diving? Oh.
ダイビング？　ああ…
So it's that time of year again...
もう そんな時期ですか
That's right.
（時田）そういうことだ
（伊織･耕平）おお!?
Chisa just accepted it...
千紗が平然と
受け入れているだと？
So, we really do need uniforms for diving?
本当に制服が必要だとは
But how are we going to use these?
しかし これをどう使うんだ？
Maybe they repel sharks.
こうすると サメよけになるとか
What are those two talking about?
あの２人
なんの話をしてるんです？
Who knows...
（寿･時田）さあ
Let me explain.
それじゃ 説明するか
This is the equipment we need for diving.
（寿）ダビングで使う機材は
大体こんな感じなんだが
WEIGHTS / SUIT / FINS, MASK, & SNORKEL
BCD / REGULATOR / DIVING COMPUTER, ETC.
Then we don't need the uniforms!
制服は必要ないじゃないですか！
やっぱりウソか！
You lied to us!
Be quiet and listen.
（寿）黙って聞け
In other words, diving...
つまり ダイビングというのは
Is expensive.
金がかかるんだよ
You understand what I'm trying to say, right?
ここまで話せば
もう分かるだろう？
This is where those come in.
そいつの使い道だ
（耕平･伊織）ふむ…
（伊織）うっ うう…
（耕平）フフ…
Their imaginations are running wild.
（千紗）なんだか すごい想像
してるみたいですけど
（寿･時田）うむ…
Have you guys heard of the Izu Spring Festival?
お前ら “伊豆(いず)春祭(はるさい)”って
知ってるか？
（伊織）はあ？
It's our school festival, held in May.
（寿）５月にやる
うちの大学の祭りのことだ
There's an event called the
"Inter-Club Men's Beauty Pageant."
（時田）“サークル対抗
ミスターコンテスト”って―
イベントがあってだな
The winning club gets some prize money.
（寿）優勝サークルには
賞金が出るんだよ
（耕平･伊織）ふーん そうですか
まさか 俺たちに出ろと？
I see. You want us to enter?
（寿･時田）正解！
（耕平･伊織）イヤだ！
-Correct!
-No!
これは男子コンテストとも言って…
-Also called the male beauty pageant.
-Or, male pageant.
男(だん)コンと略している
（耕平･伊織）最低だ！
That's terrible!
ハッ！　千紗は知ってたのか？
Did you know about this?
Well, yeah. I watched it last year.
I'm not participating.
俺は御免です
Wearing an outfit like that and getting laughed at?
No way.
そんな服を着て
笑い者になるなんて―
冗談じゃない
（伊織･千紗）ああ…
Hey, Kohei.
（時田）なあ 耕平
（耕平）ん？
You're a pretty boy.
お前は美形だ
な… 何を
What?!
If you enter, you'd probably win.
Use your charm to help our club.
お前が出れば きっと勝てる
サークルのために
お前の魅力を貸してくれないか？
えっ そう言われても…
I'm sorry, but...
-So, you guys don't need me.
-Why not?
じゃあ 俺は必要ないですよね？
（寿）なぜだ？
You have Kohei.
だって 耕平がいるじゃないですか
Hey, Iori.
なあ 伊織
What?
（伊織）なんですか
お前はネタ枠だ
（伊織）ブチ殺しますよ
-You'll enter in the joke category.
-I'll kill you.
-Put those on, you guys.
-Huh?
（寿）んじゃ ２人とも
そいつを着てくれ
（耕平･伊織）え？
（寿）今日は実際に海に出る
We're going to the ocean today.
How is the size?
（時田）サイズはどうだ？
It's a little tight.
ちょっと苦しい程度ですね
As long as there're no gaps, it's fine.
（時田）
隙間ができていなければＯＫだ
Let's go.
じゃあ 行くぞ！
Okay.
（耕平）うっす
ハァ… 海か
The ocean...
Aren't you going, Chisa?
千紗は 行かないのか？
I'm watching the store.
店番
I see. Well, then...
そっか じゃ
THE OCEAN, US, AND BLUE
（千紗）あのさ 伊織
（伊織）ん？
Hey, Iori.
Were you excited when you started college life?
大学生活が始まるとき
ワクワクした？
-Huh?
-How did you feel?
（伊織）え？
（千紗）どう？
ん～ そういえば ワクワク…
Now that you mention it, I did...
feel excited...
してたな…
Then I'm sure
（千紗）それなら きっと―
you'll have fun.
楽しめると思う
（伊織）ん？
Iori will team up with me for practice.
（寿）伊織は俺と組んで練習だ
Then I'll practice with Kohei.
（時田）じゃ 俺は耕平とだな
This is really simple.
（寿）やることは至って単純
You'll simulate what it's like
to breathe underwater.
水の中で呼吸する感覚を
体験する
Okay...
はい
Put the regulator in your mouth and breathe in.
（寿）レギュをくわえて
息を吸ってみろ
Okay.
はい
How was it?
（寿）どうだ？
It feels really different from breathing normally.
普通に息をするのとは
だいぶ感覚が違いますね
（寿）そうだな　吸うと一気に
空気が流れ込んでくる感じだろ
Correct. It's as if the air flows in
all at once when you breathe in.
That's true.
（伊織）それもありますが―
You have to use force to breathe in.
息を吸うときに若干
力がいるというか…
Yeah. You might have a hard time
breathing until you get used to it.
（寿）ああ 慣れないうちは
意識しないと―
呼吸に詰まるかもなあ
（伊織）はい
-Okay.
-Let's try actually diving underwater.
じゃ 実際に潜ってみるか
Okay...
分かりました
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
Iori...
（寿）伊織？
（伊織）プハッ！　ハァ ハァ…
Hey, Iori.
なあ 伊織
What?
（伊織）なんですか…
Why are you out of breath?
なぜ 息を切らしてるんだ？
Because I can't breathe.
苦しいからです
Then why are you carrying
that tank on your back?
（寿）お前は なんのために
タンクを背負ってる
I'm scared of breathing underwater.
（伊織）怖いんですよ
水の中で息を吸うってことが
-Scared?
-Yes.
（寿）怖い？
（伊織）はい…
I see. Well, you might feel confused at first,
but you'll get used to it.
（寿）そうか まあ―
最初は戸惑うかもしれないが
すぐに慣れるさ
Then I'll try it one more time.
じゃあ もう１回やってみます
（伊織）プハッ…
What's wrong? Are you okay?
どうした 大丈夫か？
Water leaked into my mask...
（伊織）マスクの中に水が…
Maybe it's too loose. Let me see.
（寿）つけ方がゆるいのかもな
貸してみろ
Thank you very much!
（奈々華(ななか)）ありがとうございました
（伊織）あれ
あのお客さんたち…
-Who are those customers?
-Wait up!
Oh. They came to dive before their business trip.
ああ 出張前に潜りに来たらしい
That looks rough.
なんか大変そうですね
They look really busy,
but they even brought their suits.
忙しそうなのに
わざわざスーツまで持ってきて
（寿）ハハハ 頼もしいだろ
（伊織）頼もしい？
-It's reassuring, right?
-Reassuring?
It's true, right?
だってそうだろ？
あの人たちは―
They're spending their
precious money and time on diving.
貴重な金や時間を使ってまで
潜ってる
In other words...
それって つまり―
it proves just how alluring this place is!
ここには それほどの魅力が
詰まっているという証拠じゃないか
（寿）さっき 水の中が
怖いと言ったな
You said it's scary underwater, right?
-Sorry.
-You don't have to apologize.
（伊織）すみません
（寿）謝ることはないさ
Even I get scared when I think about what would happen
if I run out of air.
水中で空気がなくなったらなんて
考えたら 俺だって怖い
Do you know what this is?
これ なんだか分かるか？
-Uh...
-This is called an octopus.
えっと…
（寿）こいつは
オクトパスといって―
It's a spare regulator.
予備のレギュレーターだ
You give it to your buddy if they run out of air.
水中で仲間が空気切れを
起こしたときに 渡してやるんだ
And the weight belt always faces the same way.
ウエイトのベルトは
つける向きが決まっているが―
これにも理由がある
There's a reason for that too.
It's so you can remove it quickly
if something happens.
何かがあったとき
手早く外してやるためだ
自分の安全だけじゃなく―
It's not only for your own safety.
It's so you can help the friends you dive with.
一緒に潜る仲間を
助けられるように
We did a thorough safety check.
安全確認はしっかりやった
You're not here alone. I'm here too.
ここには お前だけじゃなくて
俺もいる
You'll be fine, so be tough and go dive.
大丈夫だから
根性入れて潜ってこい
I'll help you, no matter what.
何があろうと助けてやる
All right!
よし！
-Here I go!
-Yeah.
いってきます！
おう！
（伊織）あっ… あれ できた
苦しくない 全然！
Huh? I did it!?
It's not tough at all!
I did it!
やった！
So this is...
これが 水の中…
what it's like underwater.
A new world...
俺の 知らなかった世界！
I didn't know about.
（伊織）ハァ ハァ…
（千紗）んっ!?
-Chisa!
-Iori?
（伊織）千紗！
（千紗）伊織？
I understand what you were trying to say now!
（伊織）分かったよ
お前が言ってたこと
海の中で息ができるって
すごいな！
It's amazing to be able to breathe underwater!
-And I can't even swim!
-Oh, really...
俺 全然泳げないのに！
（千紗）そ… そう
So, this is what it means to experience
a new world!
これが 新しい世界に
触れるってことなんだな！
So, this is how it feels to go to outer space
and experience zero gravity!
これって あれか！
宇宙に行って―
無重力を体験するような
感覚なのか！
-Iori, I know. Now go change...
-I wonder if it feels like
（千紗）伊織 分かったから
とりあえず着替えて
（伊織）やっぱり
本格的に潜ると―
-you're floating when you really get into diving...
-People
浮遊感とか
そういうのと…
（時田）あればっかりは―
who only choose what they know
will never experience that joy.
できることだけ選んでるやつには
一生 分からん喜びだな
What do you mean?
なんのことですか？
-You don't understand?
-I'm talking about this, of course!
（寿）お前は分からないか？
そりゃお前 あれだよ
It's the joy of learning how to do
something you couldn't do before.
できないことが できるようになる
喜びってやつだ
Cheers!
（一同）カンパーイ！
クゥー！
-That was good!
-It burns.
（耕平）う… うまい
（寿）染みるだろ
Have some food with your drinks.
（登志夫(としお)）ほれ つまみだ
（一同）おおー！
Thanks!
ありがとうございます
That was great, Iori.
（時田）よかったな 伊織
苦手を克服できて
You conquered your fear.
I'm still not great in the water.
まだ 水は苦手ですけど
But you learned how fun it is
to step into a new world!
だが 新しい世界に踏み込む
楽しさを知ることはできただろ？
Yeah! Thank you.
はい！
ありがとうございました
No, you don't have to thank us.
いやいや 礼には及ばんさ
そうだとも これで…
Right. Now...
あ…
There's no reason for you
to say no to this new world either!
（寿）こっちの新世界を
断る理由もなくなったわけだしな
No!
（伊織）イヤだー！
ううっ またしても飲みすぎた…
I drank too much again...
Water...
水… ウプッ
What are you doing?
何すんですか… えっ？
ヒイイ…
Let's stay in bed a bit longer.
（梓(あずさ)）もうちょい寝ようよ
（伊織）え？
Huh? Uh... Huh?
え？　は？　え？
（伊織）はあ!?
（梓）ううん…
This can't be real.
（伊織）いやいや ありえないだろ
Getting drunk and waking up to
someone half-naked sleeping next to me...
酔って起きたら
隣で半裸の人が寝てるなんて…
（寿と時田のいびき）
Is a normal thing now..
（伊織）いつものことだな
I mean... Who is she?
というか この人は一体？
-Oh. This is the first time you guys met.
-Whoa!
ああ お前らは初対面か
（耕平）うおお！
You know that our club
is an intercollegiate club, right?
うちがインカレサークル
だってことは―
INTERCOLLEGIATE CLUB:
A CLUB WITH MEMBERS FROM DIFFERENT COLLEGES
知ってるよな？
So, she's from another school?
（伊織）てことは ほかの
学校の人なんですか？
（時田）こいつは青海(おうみ)女子大の
浜岡(はまおか)梓って女でな
She's Azusa Hamaoka from Oumi Women's University.
Why is she sleeping here?
（耕平）で その人が
なんで寝てるんですか？
Maybe because there was a futon.
（時田）
布団があったからじゃないか？
I was sleeping in that futon first...
（伊織）その布団
先に俺が寝ていたんですが…
（時田）そういうことを
気にする女じゃない
She's not the type of girl to care about that.
（伊織）うわっ…
（耕平）普通―
Whoa.
Who would take off their clothes
and sleep in a room with naked guys?
裸の男がいる部屋で
服脱いで寝るか？
That's what I mean.
（寿）そういうこった
If you treat her like a girl,
you'll make a fool out of yourself.
こいつを女扱いしていると
バカを見るぞ
あ… 服を着るなんて
珍しいですね
You're wearing clothes? That's unusual.
We have something to do outside today.
今日は外で
やることがあるからな
That's why we invited Azusa.
（時田）そのために
梓を呼んだんだ
-Let's wake her up then.
-Wait.
じゃあ 起こしましょうか？
（寿）待て
（伊織）え？
先に お前らに
話しておくことがある
There's something we have to tell you first.
Something important about the Izu Spring Festival.
伊豆春祭に関する大事な話だ
Okay, done!
（梓）ほい 完成
（耕平･伊織）おおっ！
You're really good.
（千紗）相変わらず上手ですね
Not really!
それほどでも
伊豆春祭で
お好み焼きを売るんですか
We'll be selling okonomiyaki
at the Izu Spring Festival?
うん 普通にうまい！
-It's delicious!
-It has to be!
うまくなきゃ困る
The sales will go to fund our club.
売り上げを
サークル予算の足しにするからな
Today, we're going to have the freshmen
learn how to make these.
（時田）というわけで―
今日は １年生に
これを作れるようになってもらう
What about you, Tokki and Bukki?
トッキーとブッキーは？
-Oh, we're...
-Tokita! Kotobuki!
ああ 俺たちは…
（東(あずま)）時田 寿 行くぞ！
（時田）おお！
-Let's go!
-Okay.
We're going to prep the equipment.
機材の準備に行ってくる
When we're done,
we'll eat with everyone.
終わったら
みんなで食いに来るから―
So, make a lot of them.
たくさん焼いといてくれ
Okay.
分かった　じゃ 始めよっか
-Then let's begin!
-Okay.
（千紗）はい
（耕平･伊織）ん…
Let's do it, Kohei!
（伊織）やるぞ 耕平！
Leave it to me, Kitahara!
（耕平）任せろ 北原(きたはら)！
Something about the Izu Spring Festival?
（伊織）伊豆春祭の大事な話？
男コンのことじゃなくて？
It's not about the male pageant?
Actually, it is related to that...
実は それがらみなんだが…
We want you to convince Chisa.
お前らには 千紗ちゃんの
説得を頼みたい
どういうことです？
What do you mean?
There's an Izu Spring Festival
women's beauty pageant.
（時田）伊豆春祭には
ミスコンもあってな
We want Chisa to enter so that
we can get more funds for our club.
サークル予算
獲得のために
千紗ちゃんに
出てもらいたいんだ
-You want us to convince her to enter!?
-That's impossible!
まさか
その説得をやれと？
絶対に無理ですよ！
だが これで彼女が
優勝してくれたら―
But if she wins,
you guys don't have to enter
the male pageant anymore.
お前らは男コンに出る
必要がなくなる
All right! Let's do it!
（耕平･伊織）っしゃー！
やってやるぜ！
Normally, Chisa would never agree
to enter the women's beauty pageant.
（伊織）普通なら
千紗は絶対に―
ミスコン出場なんて
承諾しないだろう
Then we just have to put her
in an abnormal condition.
（耕平）ならば 普通じゃない
状態にしてやればいいだけのこと
We'll get her drunk, she'll loosen up,
（伊織）千紗を酔わせて
判断力を奪い
and we'll get her to enter the pageant!
（耕平）ミスコン参加の
言質を取る！
It's hot today, Kohei!
（伊織）いや～ 暑いな 耕平！
Right, Kitahara!
そうだな 北原！
こう暑いと熱中症が怖いな
It's so hot I'm going to get heatstroke!
We have to stay hydrated!
きちんと水分補給をしないとな！
I'll go bring something to drink!
じゃあ 俺が飲み物を
取ってきてやるよ
VODKA + WHISKEY
OOLONG TEA
-Here's some oolong tea.
-Oh, thanks.
ほーら ウーロン茶
おう サンキュー
Kitahara, got it?
The alcohol is in my right hand.
（耕平）北原 分かってるな
右手が酒だ
The right hand is for Chisa.
The left hand is for me.
（伊織）右手が千紗
左手が俺だな
Hey, Chisa. Have a drink.
ほら 千紗　飲み物
I can't stop right now.
I'll have some later.
（千紗）
今 手が離せないからあとで
Then I'll take it.
じゃあ 私がもらっちゃうね
（伊織･耕平）え？
Huh?
VODKA + WHISKEY
あ… 飲まないの？
-Aren't you going to drink?
-Well...
え… えっと その…
What? Is there something weird in it?
何？　まさか変な物でも
入ってるの？
ハ… ハハハ　まさかそんな！
Of course not!
Come on, drink up, Kitahara!
ほら 飲めよ 北原！
Yeah! You're right!
お… おう そうだな！
あ… どうしたの？　伊織
What's wrong, Iori?
Oh, nothing.
（伊織）いや なんでも…
てめえ
なんてことしてくれやがる！
You bastard! Look what you did!
It was unavoidable!
今のは不可抗力だろ！
Let's switch!
（伊織）交代だ！
（耕平）じゃ 今度は俺がやるか
I'll do it this time.
I'll bring some drinks!
なら 飲み物でも
持ってきてやるよ
フフフ…
What are you making?
（千紗）何 作ってるの？
（伊織）うっ！
（千紗）おお…
Chisa!? This isn't--
ちちち… 千紗 別にこれは！
You guys sure are pathetic.
（千紗）まったく
２人ともよくやるわ
You're trying to get Imamura to drink that, right?
それ 今村(いまむら)君に
飲ませようとしてるんでしょ？
うう…
Kohei. Here's some tea.
（伊織）耕平 お茶だ
Oh. Thanks.
おお 悪いな
ブーッ！
すまない 不可抗力だったんだ
Sorry. It was unavoidable.
How was this unavoidable!?
何がどうなったら
これが不可抗力になるんだ？
うーん 上出来 上出来！
Good job!
I'm not as good as you, though.
梓さんほど
うまく作れないですけど
It's okay!
いいの いいの
大学祭の出店なんだから
It's just for the school festival.
いやあ こういうロケーションだと
あれだな 千紗
In a setting like this...
What?
何？
-Don't you feel like having a beer?
-I knew you'd say that! So I brought some!
ビールが欲しくなるよな？
そうくると思って
用意しておいたぜっ！
I don't want any.
私はいらないけど
あっ 私もらってもいいかな？
Can I have some?
プハーッ！
君たち２人 気が利くね！
You two are really considerate!
Well, well...
それはそれは…
We're extremely delighted.
お褒めにあずかり恐悦至極…
うんうん 奈々華から聞いたとおり
かわいい後輩たちじゃない
Just like I heard from Nanaka. You're cute.
-From Nanaka?
-Are you guys close?
（伊織）奈々華さんから？
（耕平）仲いいんですか？
We talk on the phone sometimes.
ちょくちょく電話する程度にはね
That's why I know a lot about you,
だから 君のこと
よく知ってるよ 伊織君
-Iori.
-Oh.
え？　ああ…
聞かせてもらったから いろいろ
She told me lots of things.
Nanaka...
（伊織）奈々華さんから…
I have to go call my friend...
お友達に電話してこないと
（伊織）ああ…
（耕平）うおっ！
Iori. That's disgusting.
伊織 汚い
ああ… もう何してるのさ
What are you doing?
That porn and that gay porn...
It's all a misunderstanding!
あの ＡＶや男どうしのとかは
誤解で…
アハハ　大丈夫 大丈夫
It's okay!
No, it's not okay...
いや 全然大丈夫じゃ…
Actually,
実は私も どっちもイケる口なんだ
I'm okay with both too.
It's nice to meet someone who's into the same stuff!
いやあ 同じ趣味の子が
いるっていうのはいいよね
Let's talk someday, okay?
今度 いろいろ語り明かそう！
-Into the same stuff?
-She's talking about diving, right?
同じ趣味？
ダイビングのことでしょ？
うう…
Hey, Kitahara!
おい 北原！　どうでもいい話を
している場合じゃないだろ
There's no time for meaningless conversation!
This is pretty important...
いや 結構大ごとなんだが…
（梓）ムフフ…
（千紗）ん？
２人ともどうかした？
Is something wrong?
-No! Nothing!
-I'm going to get some drinks!
いやいや 別に！
ちょっと飲み物 取ってくる！
I didn't want it to come down to this...
この手だけは
使いたくなかったが…
I'll have to give everyone this...
全員の飲み物を
これにするしか…
-Here's some oolong tea!
-Here!
はい ウーロン茶
（耕平）どうぞ
-I still have some. I'm fine.
-Me too.
まだあるからいいよ
（千紗）私も
（伊織･耕平）まだまだ！
There's more!
フッ！
Shaved ice is perfect for the sea!
海といえば かき氷！
シロップは特性だぜ！
It has special syrup!
I'm full.
もう おなかいっぱいだから
You guys can have it.
君ら２人で食べなよ
２人とも
さっきから何してるのよ
What are you guys doing?
Can I ask you something?
あのさ ちょっと聞いていい？
Why are you trying to get Chii-chan drunk?
ちーちゃん酔わせて
何しようとしてんの？
What you're talking about!?
（伊織）ななな…
なんのことだか さっぱり！
That's a pretty extreme accusation!
（耕平）言いがかりも
甚だしいよなあ！
If you're trying to get her drunk, then I have an idea.
潰して何かしようっていうなら
私にも考えがあるけど？
No! That's not what we're doing!
いえ そういうんじゃないんです！
Then what were you trying to do?
なら 何しようとしてたの？
It can't be helped!
（耕平）クッ！
こうなりゃしかたない！
No more tricks! Chisa!
小細工はやめだ！　千紗！
な… 何よ？
What?
-Enter the women's beauty pageant!
-No.
（耕平･伊織）ミスコンに出てくれ
（千紗）イヤ
He'll kneel down naked and beg you! Please!
（耕平）こいつが全裸で
土下座するから頼む！
Want me to step on him?
上から踏めばいいの？
Just answer yes or no!
（伊織）せめて
“出る”“出ない”で返事を！
-Please!
-We're begging you!
（伊織）とにかく頼む！
（耕平）このとおりだ！
I said no!
（千紗）イヤったらイヤ！
That won't work. If you're going
to ask her for something,
ダメだよ
頼み事するのにそんなんじゃ
you should tell her your reason.
頼む理由も
ちゃんと言わないとね
（耕平･伊織）あ…
You don't have a reason?
（梓）理由ないの？
Well...
いやあ まあ…
If Chisa enters, we can get the prize money.
千紗が出たら 優勝賞金
ゲットできるじゃないですか
Then we don't have to enter
the male pageant.
そうすると 俺らが
男コンに出ないで済むんですよ
ふうん…
そっか なるほどね
I see. Now I understand.
What about it, Chii-chan?
どう？　ちーちゃん
No way.
絶対にイヤです
（耕平）うぬう…
I was expecting this...
（伊織）予想してはいたが…
You shouldn't have asked in the first place.
（千紗）じゃあ
最初から聞かないで
What? She said no?
なんだ ダメだったのか
We didn't even have a chance.
とりつく島もないって感じで…
So, now we have to enter the male pageant...
これで俺らは
男コン出場確定か
It can't be helped.
（寿）まあ しかたないな
そういえば 先輩たちのときは
誰が出たんですか？
Who entered the pageant when it was your turn?
Azusa entered the women's pageant.
（時田）ミスコンなら梓が出たな
She is pretty.
（伊織）確かに美人ですもんね
-She lost in the preliminaries though.
-Huh? Why?
（時田）予選落ちだったけどな
（耕平）へ？　なんで？
She forgot her swimsuit and competed in her underwear,
so she was disqualified.
水着を忘れて
下着で出て失格になった
（伊織）いろいろと
すごいですね それ
That's amazing.
She wasn't embarrassed?
羞恥心がないのか？
She's that type of girl.
（寿）あいつはそういう女だ
No, that can't...
いやいや そんな…
Well, you'll find out soon.
まあ いつもどおりにしてりゃ
分かるさ
Take it off!
（東）っしゃあ！
（横手(よこて)）
いい脱ぎっぷりじゃねえか！
（安西(あんざい)）
次 負けたらＭ字開脚な！
If you lose, you have to spread your legs!
（部員たちの騒ぎ声）
All right! I'm going to go join them.
（梓）よしっ
ちょっと まぜてもらってくる！
Go ahead.
いってらっしゃい
Azusa likes that kind of stuff.
本当に梓は
ああいうの好きよね
Let me join!
（梓）まーぜーてー！
Okay! Huh!?
あっ はい
って ええっ!?
-Really?
-Yeah.
本当ですか？
（梓）うん
It's naked rock paper scissors!
You'll strip?
だって 野球拳ですよ？
脱ぐんですよ？
Are you okay with that?
いいんですか!?
そりゃ 負ければ脱ぐよ
野球拳だもん
If you lose, you strip!
It's naked rock paper scissors!
I'm not going to get totally naked though.
さすがに全裸にはならないけどね
私だって 乙女なんだから
I'm a young girl, you know.
あ… なんだ
-Oh, yeah.
-You're right.
そりゃそうですよね
That's why...
（梓）だからちゃんと
ばんそうこうを貼ってるよ
I've stuck band-aids on.
I'll go first.
（伊織）まずは俺がいく
But, Kitahara...
だが 北原…
You have nothing left to take off.
もう 脱ぐものないだろ
（梓）ククッ…
There's nothing to worry about, Kohei.
（伊織）心配ない 耕平
Just once.
１回だ… １回だけのチャンスに
俺はすべてを懸ける！
I'm going to bet everything on just one chance.
HAIRPIN
（梓）グフフフ…
Tokki! Bukki! This guy is great!
トッキー ブッキー
この子 もう最高！
I'm glad you like him.
気に入ったようで何よりだ
He's talented, right?
すげえ逸材だろ
Let's compete on speed!
（梓）それじゃあ
スピードで勝負！
I'm going to take this one standing.
You stay back, Kohei.
（伊織）受けて立ちましょう
下がってろ 耕平！
（耕平）いや むしろ
お前が下がってろよ
No, you stay back.
（梓）あ～ おもしろかった
That was fun!
-They're nice, right?
-Yeah.
いい子たちでしょ？
（梓）うん
What's nice about them?
（千紗）あれの
どこがいい子なんだか…
I like them, though.
私は気に入ったけどね
-Hey, Chii-chan.
-Yes?
ねえ ちーちゃん
（千紗）はい
（梓）ミスコンくらい
出てあげれば？
Why don't you enter the women's beauty pageant?
No.
イヤです
-It's part of the joy of being born a woman.
-What do you mean?
女冥利(みょうり)に尽きると思うけどねえ
（千紗）どこがですか
んー だってほら
You know...
Those guys never doubted
that you'd win, right?
あの子たち ちーちゃんの優勝を
信じて疑わなかったでしょ？
It's because they think
you're the cutest one, Chii-chan.
それって ちーちゃんが一番
かわいいと思ってるからじゃない
If Chisa enters, we can get the prize money.
千紗が出たら 優勝賞金
ゲットできるじゃないですか
ん…
What do you think?
（梓）どう？
-Well...
-Huh?
（千紗）別に…
（梓）ん？
It's not that I won't do it no matter what...
何がなんでも絶対にイヤって
わけじゃないですけど
I just don't like how
they're trying to embarrass only me.
ただ 私にだけ恥ずかしい思いを
させようっていう―
考え方が気に入らないんです
（梓と奈々華の笑い声）
HEARTTHROB
LEMON SOUR
-What?
-You're right.
（千紗）なんですか
そりゃそうよね
確かに男らしくないわ
That's not very manly.
（梓）それなら こうしようよ
（千紗）ん？
Then let's do this.
Thanks to Iori and Kohei,
伊織と耕平のおかげで
Chisa decided to enter the women's beauty pageant.
無事 千紗ちゃんが
ミスコンに出ることになった
（伊織）えっ？　マジですか！
-Really?
-She changed her mind overnight?
ひと晩で心変わり！
So, there's something we want to give you.
（寿）ついては２人に渡す物がある
（耕平･伊織）お？
Here. Take this.
（時田）さあ 受け取ってくれ
（耕平･伊織）なんでだ！
Why?!
千紗ちゃんから ミスコン参加に
あたって条件を出されてな
Chisa said she'd enter the women's beauty pageant
under one condition.
You guys have to enter the male pageant.
お前らも男コンに出ることだそうだ
Then why did we even...
じゃあ 俺たちはなんのために！
むだな行動じゃねえか！
It was all for nothing!
-You wear the girl's uniform!
-You're the one entering the joke category!
せめてお前が この女子のを！
ネタ系はお前だろうが！
They look like they're having fun.
楽しそうだな
I'm glad they're close.
仲がよくて何よりだ
-Everything's okay now, right?
-Yes.
これなら全部オッケーでしょ？
（千紗）はい
Well, I feel a little better now.
まあ ちょっとスッとしました
（伊織と耕平の騒ぎ声）
DEEP BLUE AL FINE
KAYA MIZUKI
Here's your mic, Kitahara.
（耕平）ほれ 北原 マイク
（伊織）俺もかよ
Me, too...? All right, let's do this!
よっしゃ いくぜ！
-Yeah, sing your heart out.
-You guys seem to be having fun.
（寿）おお～ 歌え歌え！
（時田）ノリノリだな
♪～
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of areppegio
If life sparkles only to the beat
of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Cheers!
～♪
（一同）
すいませんでした！
We're very sorry!
Izu Spring Festival! Yay!
（一同）
伊豆春祭じゃ！　イエーイ！
Peek a Boo(ピーカブー)の
古手川(こてがわ)千紗です
I'm Chisa Kotegawa
from Peek-a-Boo!
どりゃあ！
Take this!
うっ！
（耕平）うおっ！　お化け！
A ghost!
NEXT EPISODE
"THE MALE BEAUTY PAGEANT"